# Stephanie Galindo

stephanimatedworld@gmail.com | (209) 270-7748 | Stockton, CA 95212

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Self-motivated Web developer and Graphic Designer with a high level of experience working on multiple projects. Passionate and hardworking with a penchant for meeting deadlines. Interested in a role with a company promoting best practices and offering diverse customer projects.

#### **WEBSITES LINKS**

• Github:

https://github.com/StephanieGalindo10

• Web Developer Portfolio:

https://stephaniegalindo10.github.io/Bootstrap-Portfolio/

• Media Portfolio:

https://github.com/StephanieGalindo10

• Linkedin:

www.linkedin.com/in/stephanie-galindo-110194103

#### **WORK HISTORY**

Amazon. Tracy, CA

Amazon Associate | 08/2017 - Current

This position exemplifies the skills needed to properly select, package, and ship our clients' orders. In the Amazon Career Program to study Full Stack Web Developer.

- Managed team performance by training, mentoring, disciplining and motivating employees. Appeals Panelist For Rehire
- Won Benchmark on Production Multiples for fastest packer rate 221% average is 120% and Best Pack over 117% Production Rate Won Benchmark on Production Outbound in Singles beat Front half Manager

Too Many Guppies Retail Store. Belen, NM *Co-Founder And Advertising Assistant | 06/2013 - 04/2018* Co-founder of Too Many Guppies a geek theme craft store. Created greek theme products. Responsibilities including marketing, graphic designer, provided administrative support, Inventory, and organized promotional events at Comic convention and on school campuses.

- Coordinated content, designs and periodic updates to the company Facebook and Esty store.
- Assisted with the design of print materials such as flyers and ads.

#### **SKILLS**

Experienced in Product
Management, Retail, and Web
Development.

Languages: Fluent in English and Spanish( Reading and Writing)
Technical Skills

- Programming Technologies: Experience t in HTML/CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Reactjs, and Bootstrap, MySQL, and MongoDB
- Version Control: Git and Github
- Visual Design: Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator)
- Video Editing: Premiere Pro and Final Cut Pro

# **EDUCATION**

The University Of California, Davis Sacramento, CA 2019

Full Stack Web Developer
Certification: Web Development
The UC Davis Full Stack Coding
Bootcamp course covers theory
and application of web
development. Major
Technologies: MERN Stack:
MongoDB, Express.js, React.js,
and Node.js. JavaScript, jQuery,
MySQL, CSS, HTML

Amazon Web Services : Loft San Francisco, CA 2019

Amazon Sumerian: Build AR & VR Applications BootCamp:

The University Of New Mexico. Albuquerque, NM Admissions Representative | 10/2016 - 07/2017 Responsibilities include the coordination, preparation, scanning, and retrieval of everyday documentation. Resolve problems and inconsistencies with data, perform limited data analysis, and prepare and generates various reports.

- Collaborated with various departments to put together activities, presentations, and meetings for potential enrollees.
- Obtained documents, clearances, certificates and approvals from local, state and federal agencies.

Walt Disney World. **Orlando, FL**DCP Internship Retail Merchandiser And Food Service | 01/2016 - 08/2016

Stock all the merchandise, cashier, and log in all delivery for guest at home or resorts. Help with guest needs including activating Disney Magic Band with online app's. Food Service included giving guest their meals, counter stocking food, busser to keep the western environment for our guest.

- Completed Marketing Certification from DCP Classes.
- Maintained records related to sales, returns and inventory availability.
- Monitored self-checkout systems and provided assistance or intervention where required.

The University Of New Mexico. Albuquerque, NM Marketing Assistant | 07/2014 - 12/2015

Keep the marketing database up-to-date by inputting new data, updating old records and inventory. Marketing company products and services to customers. Design posters, flyers, web graphics for clients including local events. Photographer of product shots and fashion photographer.

- Edited, toned, captioned and uploaded photographs for advertising publications.
- Coordinated meetings between project members and clients to develop ideas, discuss progress and set goals.
- Carefully proofread labels and sales materials prior to printing.

# **VOLUNTEER**

Volunteer Work

Organization: UC Davis Continuing and Professional Education Student Mentor Program

## **AFFILIATIONS**

Women Who Code

- Member, Women Who Code, 2018 to Current
- Member, Phi Theta Kappa Honor Society

Amazon Web Services

The University Of New Mexico Albuquerque, NM 2015

Bachelor Of Applied Science In Media Arts: Media Arts

- Member of Phi Theta Kappa Honor Society
- Graduated with 3.9 GPA

The University Of New Mexico Los Lunas, NM 2014

Associate's Degree: Digital Communications And Multimedia With Animation

- Member of Phi Theta Kappa Honor Society
- Graduated with 3.9 GPA

### **PROJECTS**

Physics Twilight Game App: February 2019
I wanted to create a game that allow user to guess a letter. The game will display each incorrect guess the user makes. Technologies used HTML,CSS, and JavaScript

Silent Hill Clicky-Application: January 2019

The app should keep track of the user's score. Every time an image is clicked, the images rendered to the page should shuffle themselves in a random order. Technologies used HTML,CSS, Bootstrap and Reactjs

Trivia Game Application:
November 2018
I created Trivia game the player
will have a limited amount of
time to finish the quiz. The game
ends when the time runs out.
Technologies used HTML,CSS,
Bootstrap and JavaScript